Corn Trading Hours:

Pit trading is from 10:30-2:15 EST or 9:30-1:15 central time

that is for all grains. electronic trading is from 7pm to 8:15 am EST

Tricia: 0.01 lot of Corn and Wheat is equivalent to 50 units. You can find the profit/loss in pips and times by 50 for 0.01 trade.
Tricia: 0.01 lot of Soybean is equivalent to 6 unit. You can find the profit/loss in pips and times by 6 for 0.01 trade.